(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
Come to your senses! Okay?
استعد وعيك! حسناً؟
Se-ah! Please come to your senses!
سيه! أرجوك عد إلى رشدك!
Lim Na-ri! Damn you!
ليم ناري! تباً لك!
I swear I'll kill you if anything happens to Se-ah!
أقسم أنني سأقتلك إذا حدث أي مكروه لسي-آه!
Se-ah!
سيه!
Hey!
يا!
HA-YOUNG
ها-يونغ
Geon-woo! It's me, Ha-joon's sister.
جيون وو! أنا أخت ها جون.
I'll send the address. Bring Se-ah here now!
سأرسل العنوان. أحضروا سيه إلى هنا الآن!
Geon-woo.
جيون وو.
Se-ah, wait.
انتظر، انتظر.
Just
فقط
hang up now.
أغلق الخط الآن.
-Geon-woo, are you still there? -Don't trust that call.
- جيون وو، هل ما زلت هناك؟ - لا تثق بتلك المكالمة.
Geon-woo.
جيون وو.
Come to the address I just sent. You'll see a lantern light. Hurry!
تعال إلى العنوان الذي أرسلته للتو. سترى ضوء فانوس. أسرع!
That's not Ha-joon's sister.
هذه ليست أخت ها جون.
Hang up now.
أغلق الخط الآن.
Listen to me, Geon-woo!
استمع إليّ يا جيون وو!
Don't listen to her.
لا تستمع إليها.
You're the only one who can save Se-ah now!
أنتِ الوحيدة القادرة على إنقاذ سي-آه الآن!
You're all Se-ah has now!
أنت كل ما تملكه سيه الآن!
Leave now!
غادر الآن!
IF WISHES COULD KILL
لو كانت الأمنيات قادرة على القتل
Se-ah.
سيه.
Yoo Se-ah.
يو سي آه.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Se-ah.
سيه.
Don't come near me!
لا تقترب مني!
I said don't come near me!
قلتُ لا تقترب مني!
Not the first time she's like this.
ليست هذه المرة الأولى التي تتصرف فيها هكذا.
Considering what I did, I had this coming.
بالنظر إلى ما فعلته، فقد استحققت هذا.
Se-ah.
سيه.
You still don't know why you're here?
ألا تزال لا تعرف لماذا أنت هنا؟
Did you forget everything again?
هل نسيت كل شيء مرة أخرى؟
Then
ثم
do you remember anything?
هل تتذكر أي شيء؟
How much do you remember?
ما مقدار ما تتذكره؟
Don't force yourself to remember. Take your time.
لا تجبر نفسك على التذكر. خذ وقتك.
The…
ال…
the gym…
الصالة الرياضية…
The gym?
الصالة الرياضية؟
Maybe it was some kind of storage room?
ربما كانت نوعاً من غرف التخزين؟
Storage room?
غرفة تخزين؟
Where was it?
أين كان ذلك؟
The place Do Hye-ryung filmed her wish video?
أين صوّرت دو هي ريونغ فيديو أمنيتها؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I was a total lunatic back then, wasn't I?
كنت مجنوناً تماماً في ذلك الوقت، أليس كذلك؟
But you know, I was totally out of my mind.
لكن كما تعلم، كنتُ فاقداً لعقلي تماماً.
Please forgive me, Se-ah.
أرجو أن تسامحني يا سيه.
Geon-woo, the red phone! Where is it? Did you find it?
جيون وو، الهاتف الأحمر! أين هو؟ هل وجدته؟
We were supposed to get rid of that phone. Did you find it?
كان من المفترض أن نتخلص من ذلك الهاتف. هل وجدته؟
Ha-joon! Did your brother-in-law get to a hospital?
هاجون! هل وصل صهرك إلى المستشفى؟
He was badly hurt. Was he treated at a hospital?
لقد أصيب بجروح بالغة. هل تلقى العلاج في المستشفى؟
-Is he okay? -Se-ah!
-هل هو بخير؟ -سيه!
-Se-ah, calm down. -Huh?
-سيه، اهدأ. -هاه؟
It's all over now.
انتهى كل شيء الآن.
Take a look at this.
ألق نظرة على هذا.
The Girigo app and the timer are both gone.
اختفى كل من تطبيق Girigo والمؤقت .
Se-ah.
سيه.
You and my sister got rid of it together.
تخلصتِ أنتِ وأختي منه معاً.
Huh?
هاه؟
You should check your phone too.
يجب عليك التحقق من هاتفك أيضاً.
My phone…
هاتفي…
Huh?
هاه؟
So are we really done with it all?
هل انتهينا من كل شيء حقاً؟
Yeah.
نعم.
How many times did I do that to you?
كم مرة فعلت ذلك بك؟
I don't know. I don't mind.
لا أعرف. لا أمانع.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Na-ri.
ناري.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
What I did was even worse.
ما فعلته كان أسوأ من ذلك.
If you knew, I bet you'd be out to kill me for real.
لو كنت تعلم، أراهن أنك ستسعى لقتلي فعلاً.
Hey, the next birthday coming up is…
أهلاً، عيد الميلاد القادم هو...
-Se-ah's.
-سيه'س.
Are you guys kidding me? Do you even know my birthday?
هل تمزحون معي؟ هل تعرفون حتى تاريخ ميلادي؟
-Doesn't yours come after the next one? -Wow.
- ألا يأتي دورك بعد الدور التالي؟ - يا للعجب.
Didn't yours already pass?
ألم تجتز اختبارك بالفعل؟
What's Kim Geon-woo saying now?
ماذا يقول كيم غون وو الآن؟
-It didn't? -You're unbelievable, seriously.
-ألم يحدث ذلك؟ -أنت لا تصدق، حقاً.
MULTIMEDIA ROOM
غرفة الوسائط المتعددة
ASBESTOS REMOVAL KEEP OUT
إزالة الأسبستوس - ممنوع الدخول
Se-ah, what's wrong?
سيه، ما الخطب؟
The bars that were here…
الحانات التي كانت هنا...
Se-ah.
سيه.
Please.
لو سمحت.
They took it down after the construction. Don't you remember?
أزالوه بعد الانتهاء من البناء. ألا تتذكر؟
The construction that stopped before we enrolled
توقف البناء قبل التحاقنا بالجامعة
suddenly finished?
انتهى فجأة؟
That makes no sense.
هذا لا معنى له.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Hey, are you okay?
مرحباً، هل أنت بخير؟
Se-ah.
سيه.
You're all Se-ah has now!
أنت كل ما تملكه سيه الآن!
Geon-woo.
جيون وو.
Hang up.
يشنق.
I told you to hang up!
قلت لك أغلق الخط!
I'll leave right now!
سأغادر الآن!
Se-ah.
سيه.
Sir, we'll get out here.
سيدي، سنخرج من هنا.
So you're the one who ran from the curse.
إذن أنت من هرب من اللعنة.
Don't do this, Na-ri.
لا تفعلي هذا يا ناري.
When a wish is granted, a price must be paid.
عندما تتحقق الأمنية، يجب دفع ثمن.
You have to follow the rules.
عليك اتباع القواعد.
Come to the address I just sent. You'll see a lantern light. Hurry!
تعال إلى العنوان الذي أرسلته للتو. سترى فانوسًا مضاءً. أسرع!
Se-ah, just hold on a little longer.
سيه، فقط اصمد قليلاً.
Please hang in there, okay?
أرجوك اصبر، حسناً؟
Hold on.
يتمسك.
1 MINUTE, 50 M BAEKUN-RO, SEORIN-SI
1 دقيقة، 50 م بايكون-رو، سيورين-سي
That way.
بهذه الطريقة.
DESTINATION
وجهة
Huh?
هاه؟
Light.
ضوء.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Geon-woo.
جيون وو.
Se-ah.
سيه.
Struggle all you want.
كافح كما تشاء.
Se-ah will die anyway.
سيموت سيه على أي حال.
Shut the fuck up!
اخرس!
Se-ah's not gonna die!
سي-آه لن يموت!
I'm…
أنا أكون…
I'm going to save
سأقوم بالحفظ
Se-ah!
سيه!
Se-ah, don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I swear I won't leave you alone this time.
أقسم أنني لن أتركك وحدك هذه المرة.
Whatever happens, I'm with you to the end.
مهما حدث، سأكون معك حتى النهاية.
Se-ah, hang on a bit longer.
سيه، انتظر قليلاً.
I'm begging you.
أتوسل إليك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Please save Se-ah, no matter what.
أرجوكم أنقذوا سيه، مهما كان الثمن.
The god of heaven set the sun and moon, and the god of life and wealth proclaimed
إله السماء وضع الشمس والقمر، وإله الحياة والثروة أعلن
that between heaven and earth, no evil spirit may deceive humans.
أنه بين السماء والأرض، لا يمكن لأي روح شريرة أن تخدع البشر.
Why…
لماذا…
This was not the maehyung?
ألم يكن هذا هو maehyung؟
Ha-young.
ها يونغ.
I'm sorry, Se-ah.
أنا آسف يا سيه.
I failed.
لقد فشلت.
I broke the maehyung with an arrow, but the curse won't stop.
لقد حطمت maehyung بسهم، لكن اللعنة لن تتوقف.
Then what do we do now?
إذن ماذا نفعل الآن؟
I've never seen this, so I don't know.
لم أرَ هذا من قبل، لذا لا أعرف.
All I know is the longer we stay here, the more dangerous it gets.
كل ما أعرفه هو أنه كلما طالت مدة بقائنا هنا، كلما ازداد الوضع خطورة.
We need to make a door and leave now.
علينا أن نفتح باباً ونغادر الآن.
Ha-young!
ها يونغ!
Ha-young.
ها يونغ.
Do Hye-ryung.
دو هاي ريونغ.
Was Do Hye-ryung freed from the curse?
هل تحررت دو هي ريونغ من اللعنة؟
There was one in front of me and one behind me.
كان هناك واحد أمامي وواحد خلفي.
Why did it go out of its way to come all the way in here?
لماذا بذل هذا الشيء كل هذا الجهد ليأتي إلى هنا؟
The Multimedia Room.
غرفة الوسائط المتعددة.
Do Hye-ryung wanted to tell us
أرادت دو هي ريونغ أن تخبرنا
that she wasn't the one who created Girigo.
أنها لم تكن هي من خلقت جيريجو.
It was Kwon Si-won.
كان كوون سي وون.
If Kwon Si-won really created the curse,
إذا كان كوون سي وون هو من تسبب باللعنة فعلاً،
we need to find the maehyung where she made her wish.
نحتاج إلى إيجاد maehyung حيث تمنت أمنيتها.
To use this method without Bangwool, I must leave and come back in.
لاستخدام هذه الطريقة بدون بانغ وول، يجب أن أغادر ثم أعود.
What method?
ما هي الطريقة؟
No one can beat Kwon Si-won here.
لا أحد يستطيع هزيمة كوون سي وون هنا.
While I use a deolmi to hold Kwon Si-won down,
بينما أستخدم deolmi لتثبيت كوون سي وون،
you go to the place Do Hye-ryung pointed to
تذهب إلى المكان الذي أشارت إليه دو هي ريونغ
and find the real red phone.
واعثر على الهاتف الأحمر الحقيقي.
That's the only way to break the curse.
هذه هي الطريقة الوحيدة لكسر اللعنة.
It may be broken, but cover your face with it.
قد يكون مكسوراً، لكن غطِ وجهك به.
You won't be noticed until I return.
لن يلاحظك أحد حتى أعود.
I'm counting on you.
أنا أعتمد عليك.
Si-won!
أرك لاحقًا!
Kwon Si-won!
كوون سي وون!
What are you doing there by yourself?
ماذا تفعل هناك بمفردك؟
Do Hye-ryung?
دو هي ريونغ؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
But how?
لكن كيف؟
The red phone.
الهاتف الأحمر.
Where is it?
أين هي؟
I'm sure she pointed to the Multimedia Room.
أنا متأكدة من أنها أشارت إلى غرفة الوسائط المتعددة.
I said let's go together, Si-won.
قلتُ: لنذهب معًا يا سي وون.
Where to?
إلى أين؟
Where else?
أين أيضاً؟
Where dead people go.
إلى أين يذهب الموتى.
How could we go? We're bound to our wishes.
كيف لنا أن نذهب؟ نحن مقيدون برغباتنا.
Then I'll go alone.
سأذهب وحدي إذن.
Hey, Hye-ryung.
مرحباً، هاي ريونغ.
Se-ah.
سيه.
The incense on you smells…
رائحة البخور التي تفوح منك...
different from the one at my place.
يختلف عن الموجود في منزلي.
Na-ri.
ناري.
You're Na-ri, right?
أنت ناري، أليس كذلك؟
So why?
فلماذا؟
You wanna know why?
هل تريد أن تعرف لماذا؟
I remembered.
تذكرت.
You guys
يا رفاق
stabbed me in the stomach to kill me.
طعنني في بطني ليقتلني.
Na-ri, back then…
ناري، في ذلك الوقت...
We had no choice back then.
لم يكن لدينا خيار في ذلك الوقت.
Back then, you--
في ذلك الوقت، أنت...
Na-ri!
ناري!
Na-ri.
ناري.
You had no choice?
لم يكن لديك خيار؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm sure you had no choice.
أنا متأكد من أنه لم يكن لديك خيار آخر.
Just like right now.
تمامًا كما هو الحال الآن.
Using the excuse of not wanting to hurt anyone's feelings,
متذرعاً بعدم الرغبة في إيذاء مشاعر أي شخص،
you told your friends things you didn't mean.
لقد أخبرت أصدقاءك بأشياء لم تكن تقصدها.
You knew I liked Geon-woo long before you did,
كنتَ تعلم أنني معجب بجون وو قبل وقت طويل من معرفتك أنت بذلك،
but you still lied about your relationship.
لكنك مع ذلك كذبت بشأن علاقتك.
Did you have fun?
هل استمتعت؟
Na-ri.
ناري.
I wasn't trying to lie about it.
لم أكن أحاول الكذب بشأن ذلك.
-I was gonna tell you, but-- -Again!
كنت سأخبرك، لكن ... مرة أخرى!
You and your fucking "I was gonna."
أنت وعبارتك اللعينة "كنت سأفعل".
Fucking excuses.
أعذار سخيفة.
So it was you.
إذن أنت كنت أنت.
The one who kept barging into my space.
الشخص الذي كان يقتحم مساحتي الشخصية باستمرار.
Fucking hell!
يا للهول!
Na-ri, please stop.
ناري، من فضلك توقفي.
You, me, and Hyeong-wook. We all did it without knowing.
أنت وأنا وهيونغ ووك. فعلنا ذلك جميعاً دون أن ندري.
I know you regret it, Lim Na-ri!
أعلم أنك نادم على ذلك يا ليم نا ري!
So please stop.
لذا من فضلك توقف.
Regret?
يندم؟
It's not regret. It's just so unfair.
ليس ندمًا. إنه أمرٌ ظالمٌ للغاية.
If Choi Hyeong-wook, that otaku loser,
لو كان تشوي هيونغ ووك، ذلك الخاسر الأوتاكو،
hadn't told us about that damn Girigo,
لم يخبرنا عن ذلك اللعين جيريجو،
none of this would've happened to me!
لم يكن ليحدث لي أي من هذا!
Please.
لو سمحت.
Is that it?
هل هذا كل شيء؟
You think it's unfair?
أتظن أن هذا غير عادل؟
"Kwon Si-won."
"كوون سي وون".
Si-won.
لهم.
Let's put an end to this.
فلنضع حداً لهذا الأمر.
You're the one who started it.
أنت من بدأ الأمر.
Why the hell should I?
لماذا عليّ أن أفعل ذلك بحق الجحيم؟
It's not the arrow.
ليس السهم.
I became a deolmi to hold you down.
أصبحتُ أداةً لإبقائك تحت السيطرة.
The more my blood soaks the thread,
كلما ازداد دمي تغلغلاً في الخيط،
the tighter it holds you.
كلما ازداد إحكام قبضته عليك.
GIRIGO MAKE A WISH
يوناني يحقق أمنية
I found it.
لقد وجدته.
Ha-young!
ها يونغ!
GIRIGO MAKE A WISH
يوناني يحقق أمنية
Se-ah!
سيه!
No.
لا.
Se-ah.
سيه.
Is it
هل هذا صحيح؟
all over now?
انتهى كل شيء الآن؟
Yes.
نعم.
It's all over now.
انتهى كل شيء الآن.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
All this just to delete an app.
كل هذا فقط لحذف تطبيق.
Guys.
شباب.
We'll be wrapping up this semester today.
سنختتم هذا الفصل الدراسي اليوم.
Our class has really been through a lot.
لقد مرّ صفنا بالكثير حقاً.
No one saw them coming.
لم يتوقع أحد قدومهم.
It still hurts, doesn't it?
لا يزال الأمر مؤلماً، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I know it must have weighed on all of you.
أعلم أن الأمر قد أثقل كاهلكم جميعاً.
Gomen!
غومين!
Hyeong-wook.
هيونغ ووك.
I hope you can now
أتمنى أن تتمكن من ذلك الآن
leave behind the body and mind that are in pain and sorrow
اترك وراءك الجسد والعقل اللذين يعانيان من الألم والحزن
and go to a better place.
والذهاب إلى مكان أفضل.
GIRIGO
خطأ
Se-ah, you still haven't deleted this?
أه، ألم تحذف هذا بعد؟
Is it because it reminds you of Hyeong-wook?
هل ذلك لأنه يذكرك بهيونغ ووك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
And also because of Na-ri.
وأيضًا بسبب ناري.
I should've done everything I could to return with Na-ri back then.
كان ينبغي عليّ أن أفعل كل ما بوسعي للعودة مع ناري في ذلك الوقت.
Se-ah. Don't think like that.
لا تفكر بهذه الطريقة.
You tried your best.
لقد بذلت قصارى جهدك.
GIRIGO WOULD YOU LIKE TO DELETE THIS APP?
جيريجو، هل ترغب في حذف هذا التطبيق؟
GIRIGO HAS BEEN DELETED
تم حذف الشبكة.
Let's say this is the car.
لنفترض أن هذه هي السيارة.
It pierced right through me here, even through the car door.
لقد اخترقتني هنا، حتى من خلال باب السيارة.
But it pinned me at this height where I couldn't stand or sit,
لكنها حصرتني في هذا الارتفاع حيث لم أستطع الوقوف أو الجلوس،
and the blood started gushing out.
وبدأ الدم يتدفق بغزارة.
Well, it went right through me like this.
حسناً، لقد اخترقني الأمر تماماً هكذا.
So I thought I was really going to die.
لذلك ظننت أنني سأموت حقاً.
At that moment, I started fading out.
في تلك اللحظة، بدأت أفقد وعيي.
I was crossing the river to the afterlife with the Grim Reaper, arm-in-arm.
كنت أعبر النهر إلى الحياة الآخرة برفقة ملك الموت، ذراعاً بذراع.
I almost made it across, but I heard this voice behind me.
كادت أن تصل إلى الضفة الأخرى، لكنني سمعت هذا الصوت خلفي.
"Brother-in-law!"
"شقيق الزوج!"
My brother-in-law on the other side was crying his eyes out.
كان زوج أختي من الجهة الأخرى يبكي بحرقة.
What? I swear I didn't cry!
ماذا؟ أقسم أنني لم أبكِ!
God, what do we do?
يا إلهي، ماذا نفعل؟
You so did cry. He cried, didn't he?
لقد بكيتِ بالفعل. لقد بكى، أليس كذلك؟
Seriously.
بجد.
At that moment, the first thing that came to mind was Haetsal's face.
في تلك اللحظة، كان أول ما خطر ببالي هو وجه هيتسال.
By the way, I saw it again.
بالمناسبة، لقد رأيته مرة أخرى.
When you helped Hyeong-wook move on,
عندما ساعدت هيونغ ووك على تجاوز الأمر،
I could see him.
استطعت رؤيته.
But that's not all.
لكن هذا ليس كل شيء.
I can see the power that dwells in you and even how it moves.
أستطيع أن أرى القوة الكامنة فيك، بل وكيف تتحرك.
What?
ماذا؟
Are you talking about what you told me at the hospital, brother-in-law?
هل تتحدث عما أخبرتني به في المستشفى يا صهري؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Haetsal.
مرحبًا.
Well…
حسنًا…
I think I've found a way.
أعتقد أنني وجدت طريقة.
A way for you to get out of this house.
هناك طريقة لتخرج من هذا المنزل.
Yeah.
نعم.
WHY DO YOU THINK CHOI HYEONG-WOOK DIED?
لماذا تعتقد أن تشوي هيونغ ووك قد مات؟
WELL… I'LL TELL YOU ONCE YOU BRING ME THE PHONE. LOL
حسنًا... سأخبرك حالما تحضر لي الهاتف. ههه
DID YOU FIND IT?
هل وجدته؟
I FOUND IT! IT REALLY WAS STILL THERE!
وجدتها! لقد كانت لا تزال هناك بالفعل!
050201 IS TYPING…
050201 يكتب…
SEE? WHAT DID I TELL YOU? LOL
أرأيت؟ ألم أقل لك؟ ههه
GIRIGO
خطأ
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang
ترجمة الترجمة الفرعية: سونغ إن جانغ